<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Surfacedfox&#39;s Pages</title>
    <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Surfacedfox&#39;s Pages</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © Ashe O&#39;Hawkes, 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://surfacedfox.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Translating a Forest</title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/forests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/forests/</guid>
      <description>As aptly pointed out in Jacob Geller&amp;rsquo;s video, A Thousand Ways of Seeing a Forest, videogames, or any art for that matter, are an exercise in translation; Translating an experience to an interactive form, paper, music, or words.
Jacob juxtaposes this concept with several translations of a Tang-dynasty poem, where the same Mandarin words could be interpreted in several ways when translated to English. What do the translators see, and focus on when doing so?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Rumination 2</title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/random2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/random2/</guid>
      <description>Some days I look back, to dusty little toys. Resting by cold concrete walls, they seem to still provide an unfulfilled warmth in the button eyes, of an age long gone by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Rumination 1</title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/random1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/random1/</guid>
      <description>A strange wistfulness takes over me
as the dimmed sun meets the heavy air
of a quiet moment
of hopeful despair</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s talk about mirrors and reflections.</title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/mirror-alt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/post/mirror-alt/</guid>
      <description>The ol&amp;rsquo; reliable duplicate room on the other side trick for mirrors is criminally underused, and understandably so; However, I feel that innovation related to that trick practically stopped after parallax-corrected cubemaps and screen space reflections caught on. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about that.
Parallax-corrected cubemaps are more or less perfect for 90% usecases, imo. They&amp;rsquo;re cheap, and are useful for a lot of stuff, particularly, irregular surfaces. They are pretty cool, but they&amp;rsquo;re static, so you won&amp;rsquo;t see dynamic stuff in reflections at worst, and have to recompute them at runtime for some semblance of it at best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m @surfacedfox, and I&amp;rsquo;m a creator!
Inspired to make games since I was 11, over the years I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up a multitude of skills in service of that goal. Be it designing and developing complex systems, or setting up a pipeline to facilitate a smooth development process, I can bridge the gap between the worlds of art and engineering. I believe interactivity is the future of storytelling, and that the best way to predict the future is to make it happen- so here we are!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>I generally respond in 2-12 hours. Please contact me via: E-Mail:
surfacedfox@gmail.com Discord:
fallfox#5967 Twitter:
@surfacedfox LinkedIn:
surfacedfox Telegram:
surfacedfox Session: 051799ff43eabe895dd9c882757ea6d2f1b9d20bcbf7a886886d1e03c825560562 GitHub:
surfacedfox </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://surfacedfox.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surfacedfox.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are some projects I&amp;rsquo;m proud of! Technical Assignment for Hopscotch Games: Video of the technical assessment project I worked on as a part of my job application at Hopscotch Games. Built according to this spec sheet, I&amp;rsquo;ve been told that my project far exceeded their expectations. Render Pipeline Conversion: I converted the Unity HDRP sample project to URP, gaining a massive performance boost for minimal fidelity differences! Wizards&amp;rsquo; Folly: A game I made with Team Firedreamer for GMTK Jam 2022!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
